and let's see what Peppa said eh
y vamos a ver lo que ha dicho Peppa eh
Because Peppa of course because I tell you
Porque Peppa por supuesto porque os digo
that it is very very serious it is very serious So I do
que es muy muy grave es muy grave Así
n't know I haven't even spoken to Tania
que no sé yo no he hablado ni con Tania
I don't speak to her I don't know what she's going to
yo no me hablo con ella No sé lo que va
do what she's going to stop doing what I
a hacer lo que va a dejar de hacer lo
have no idea what she's going to do but of
que no tengo ni idea qué va hac pero
course It's coming from who they
claro Es que viniendo de quién
come from forgive me for not believing
vien perdonarme que no me crea
anything I can't I can't I
nada yo no puedo yo no puedo Yo me
hit my head on the desk So it
pegado un choco con el escritorio
's very strong very strong very
O sea que es muy fuerte muy fuerte muy
strong what came out of Tania is very very
fuerte lo que ha salido de Tania es muy
very strong but of course it's coming
muy muy fuerte pero claro es que viene
from Javi Well she considers that it comes
de Javi Bueno ella considera que viene
from Javi Because it doesn't come from Javi it ​​comes from
de Javi Porque no viene de Javi viene de
Tania herself who is the one who has
la propia Tania que es la que lo ha
published it on all her networks asking for
publicado en todas sus redes pidiendo
signatures to get her husband out of jail
firmas para sacar al marido de la cárcel
And from poderjudicial.com where the
Y del poderjudicial.com que está ahí la
sentence is you can read and it's a
sentencia se puede leer y es una
horror movie eh but it's coming
película de terror eh pero es que viene
from Jai So I'm on the other side I am
de Jai Entonces yo al otro lado yo estoy
on the other side I am on the side
en el otro lado yo estoy en el lado
where the other defends itself tremendous eh
donde se defiende el otro tremendo eh es
these people can go crazy eh Nothing  you're
para volverse loco esta gente eh Nada de
welcome So it's that whoever it comes from is
nada O sea que es que de quien viene es
that eh he's been going on for I don't know how many
que eh se ha tirado yo no sé cuántos
weeks Maybe up to a couple of months
semanas Quizás hasta un par de meses
continuously saying that I enjoyed him
poniendo continuamente que yo la gozaba
sexually and that he was afraid to take
sexualmente y que tenía miedo de sacar
the dog out and that So I
al perro y que esto Entonces yo no me
can't believe anything Pepa you harassed me not
puedo creer nada [__] tú me acosaba no
sexually he harassed me I haven't said
sexualmente me acosaba yo no he dicho
anything sexual tremendous eh man they would side with whoever it was
nada sexual tremendo eh tío se pondrían
eh they would side with whatever man it's
de del lado del que fuera eh se pondrían
more than
de de lo que fuera tío es que ya más que
this man more than this that has come out
esto tío ya más que esto que ha salido
What is a continued abuse over time
Qué es un abuso continuado en el tiempo
to a minor from when she was 11 years old
a una menor desde que tenía 11 años
until she was 15 and they are crying out
hasta que tenía 15 y están poniendo el
loud because
grito en el cielo porque es que lo ha
Javi has mentioned it It's that this is
comentado Javi Es que esto es la
privacy this is their privacy man
privacidad esto es su privacidad hombre
Why don't we leave their own I mean
Por qué no dejamos la propia O sea
imagine that tomorrow a news story comes out and I've
imaginaros que mañana sale una noticia y
told you before is that almost
os lo he dicho antes es que salen casi a
daily news stories come out about aggressors of
diario noticias de agresores de
rapists Well imagine that
violadores Bueno pues imaginaros que
a news story comes out I mean this is
sale una noticia o sea esto es
exactly the same as tomorrow on Tele5
exactamente lo mismo que mañana en tele5
a news story comes out and says
salga una noticia y diga
em Well look today three m eh three  young people
em Pues mira hoy tres m eh tres jóvenes
leaving a nightclub have raped a
al salir de una discoteca han violado en
girl in an elevator and these
un ascensor a una chavala y cogen esta
people grab and go on live and say and
gente y salen en un directo y dicen y
their followers and say Oy Uy How bad
sus seguidores y dicen Oy Uy Qué malo
How bad tele5 How bad the news
Qué malo tele5 Qué malo el telediario
giving this news that belongs to the
dando esta noticia eso pertenece a la
privacy of the three kids of the
privacidad de los tres chavales de los
three of the three poor rapists Tania
tres de los tres pobres violadores Tania
brought out your sentence Javi Tania brought up to
sacó tu sentencia Javi Tania sacó hasta
the date in which I had a
la fecha en la que tenía audiencia
preliminary hearing when I had a trial when I
previa cuando he tenido juicio cuando he
had to testify in another trial that
tenido que testificar en otro juicio que
was not mine so she has brought out everything that was
no era mío tan ha sacado todo que era
private whatever she wanted and I
privado lo que le ha dado la gana y ya
tell you this is just the beginning eh but
os digo esto es solo el comienzo eh pero
like me this is going to continue it is going to continue it is going to
como yo esa va a seguir va a seguir va a
continue things are going to come out of course
seguir van a salir saliendo cosas claro
but the level is that eh the level is that it
o sea pero el nivel es ese eh el nivel
is exactly the same as
es ese es ex es exactamente lo mismo que
if tomorrow a news story comes out on
si mañana sale una noticia en el
tele5 and they say Hey look,
telediario de tele5 y dicen Oye mira
three young people have raped in a
que que han violado tres jóvenes en una
nightclub in an elevator they have raped
discoteca en un ascensor han violado a
a young woman and they take everyone start opening
una joven y cogen empiezan todos a abrir
live to say Oy Oy Oy how bad those
directos a decir Oy Oy Oy qué malos los
on the news eh How bad those on the
del informativo eh Qué malos los del
news eh poor  intimacy poor
informativo eh pobre intimidad pobre
privacy of rapists is a
privacidad de los violadores es un tema
private matter of theirs tremendous tremendous man
privado de ellos tremendo tremendo tío
what these people are doing is tremendous That's it, it
lo de esta gente es tremendo Ya está no
has no more what these people are doing is tremendous man man
tiene más lo de esta gente es tremendo
Seriously really eh And I don't know if
tío tío En serio de verdad eh Y no sé si
we'll ever do a live reading it
llegaremos a hacer un directo leyéndola
eh but the sentence is the worst thing I've ever
eh pero la sentencia es la peor cosa que
seen in my life in my almost 40 years it
he visto en la vida en mis casi 40 años
's a sentence worse than Daniel
es una sentencia peor que la de Daniel
Sancho's you can't even imagine man the
Sancho no os podéis ni imaginar tío las
atrocities he did to that girl you
atrocidades que le hizo a esa chiquilla
can't even imagine well Pablo
no os podéis ni imaginar bueno Pablo
Pablo has said some little things not on his
Pablo ha dicho alguna cosilla no en su
Twitter no e The only thing that if Tania I
Twitter no e Yo lo único que si Tania Me
imagine that it will take because I'm telling you that
imagino que tomará porque ya os digo que
the matter is very serious and very delicate very
la cosa es muy grave y muy delicada muy
delicate that's what someone told me now in
delicada eso me decía alguien ahora por
private
privado
Well I know as without with you you will have to
Bueno yo s as sin con ustedes tendrás
condemn this I'm not saying
que que condenar esto no digo yo
condemn even if I were a
condenar ni que yo fuera un
judge I condemn Javi to Javi s to Javi
juez yo condeno a Javi a Javi s a Javi
Javi who said pelca a youtuber
Javi que ha dicho pelca una youtuber
Javi to Javi we remind him that he said
Javi a Javi se lo recordamos que dij
coba a youtuber okay We don't know what
coba una youtuber vale No sabemos Qué
happened  We don't even know what the hell was going on
pasó Ni sabemos qué [__] estaba pasando
because he told him in 2019 But anyway,
porque se lo dijo en el 2019 Pero bueno
let's go until approximately 2027
vamos a hasta el 2027 aproximadamente
talking about how Javi has to be kicked off the
hablando de que Javi hay que echarlo de
internet, let's make groups, let's make a
internet vamos a hacer grupos vamos a
group, let's make a group of those
hacer un grupo vamos a hacer un grupo de
affected by Javi Oliveira and let's
afectados por Javi oliveira y Vamos a
all get in touch with YouTube
ponernos todos en contacto con YouTube
to tell them that Javi has been convicted
para decirle que a Javi lo han condenado
twice for insulting, tremendous,
dos veces por insultar tremendo
tremendous. I do not condemn, the judges condemn,
tremendo Yo no condeno condenan los
tremendous,
tremendo
tremendous. I will not condemn anything because I do
tremendo yo no condenaré nada porque yo
not have
no tengo
enough information and even if I did,
suficiente información y aunque la
I am not lying, eh, I am lying, I have nothing to
tuviera yo no mentira eh mentira tengo
condemn, nothing, nothing, they keep
por condenar nada nada me siguen
sending me anything. So if you don't have
mandando nada Entonces si no tenéis la
enough information to condemn,
suficiente información para condenar Por
why when the television factory did
qué cuando la fábrica de la tele hizo
an injustice against Antonio David, did
una injusticia contra Antonio David
you condemn if you had nothing to do with it and it
condenaste si no teníais nada que ver y
was not with you. So if you have
no iba con ustedes Entonces si no tenéis
nothing to condemn,
nada que condenar
eh, Why when you were sucking up to me, did you
eh Por qué cuando me hacíais la pelota
all condemn the stalker who published a
condenaba todos al acosador que publicó
photo of my children and stalked me, eh?
foto de mis hijos y me perseguía eh Por
Why did you all condemn him when you are sucking up to me
qué lo condenaste todos cuando me asais
if it was not with you and you
la pelota si no iba con ustedes y no
are not judges, yes, yes, you do not have  the
sois jueces si si no tenéis ustedes la
power to condemn because you have
potesta para condenar porque habéis
all given your opinion on the Daniel Sancho case
opinado todos del caso Daniel Sancho
let the judges do their job no no no
dejar que los jueces hagan su trabajo no
we do not have we
no no nosotros no tenemos nosotros
condemn no eh we condemn no
condenar no eh nosotros condenar no
Peppa we contacted Joan
Peppa nosotros contactamos con Joan
Plana eh Despite the fact that in his day
plana eh A pesar de que en su día
you supported the gameover and there is a comment
apoyaste el gameover y hay un comentario
in the gameover of yours saying that the
en el gameover tuyo diciendo que el
gameover is a masterpiece because it is
gameover es una obra maestra porque lo
okay because it is and you went to
es vale porque lo es y te fuiste a
contact John Planas privately
contactarle por privado a John planas
to take it to your channel there you do judge
para llevarlo a tu canal ahí si juzgas
but in a sexual abuse of a minor there I keep quiet
pero en un abuso sexual a una menor ahí
there I keep quiet The convicted
me callo ahí me callo El condenado de
Javi Oliveira Yes yes The convicted Javi
Javi oliveira Sí sí El condenado de Javi
Oliveira Yes yes because he said pelos escova
oliveira Sí sí porque dijo pelos escova
Uh
Uh
careful they keep sending me photos intimate photos let's
cuidado me siguen mandando fotos fotos
see lady he was already sentenced for a short
ver señora ya fue condenado por poco
time because that ex permanent prison
tiempo porque eso ex prisión permanente
exactly It's that they don't have to
exactamente Es que no tienen que
condemn anything it's that he was already sentenced the
condenar nada es que ya fue condenado el
issue is that Tania was She was
tema es que Tania estaba Estaba
collecting signatures lying saying that it
recogiendo firmas mintiendo diciendo que
was nothing that there was no proof that it was
no era nada que no había prueba que era
false testimony That's Tania and she
un testimonio falso Esa es la Tania y
was with this person that she had just
estuvo con esta persona que acababa de
met you know he's tremendous dude I'm that
conocer sees que es tremendo tío Yo es
true or rather these people
que de verdad o sea es que esta gente no
have no limits these people have no
tiene límite ninguno est gente no tiene
limits they are what they are
límite ninguno son lo que son
eh Just say one thing let's see say it I know you
eh Nada más que di una cosa a ver dila
're sending me for by md eh
Sé que me estáis mandando por por md eh
if there are proven facts let
si hay hechos probados que lo saque
whoever has to release it release it if they
quien lo tenga que sacar si es que lo
want to release it But this one that's here is not going to
quieren sacar Pero esta que está aquí no
be no matter how much you send me because
va a ser por mucho que me mandéis porque
it's a sentence no way Ah ah
es s una sentencia ni de coña Ah ah
fly Not that, not that eh not that, not that we don't
mosca Eso no eso no eh eso no de eso no
talk about eh Not that, not that Well if she
hablamos eh Eso no eso no Bueno pues si
bit her herself in Chain let
le picó ella misma en Chain que vaya la
people go to Chain and look at it I'm not going to No I'm
gente a Chain y lo mire yo no voy a No
not going to get into that it's not Javi's not
en eso no voy a entrar no es de Javi no
Javi's not no way No no way it's not
es de Javi ni de coña No ni de coña no
Javi's if it were it were it were that a
es de Javi si que fuera que fuera que un
youtuber has sued Javi for
youtuber ha demandado a Javi por
insults that it were it were it were that a
insultos que fuera que fuera que un
youtuber has sued Jai for calling him an
youtuber ha demandado a Jai por decirle
[ __ ] or for saying Uy you have a
[__] o por decirle Uy tienes el
black eye or things like that Uy there we
ojo morado o cosas de esas Uy ahí í
open 18 live everyone that it
abrimos 18 directos todo el mundo que
was a Private thing of  Javi who was
fuera una cosa Privada de Javi que fuera
an uncle of Javi a cousin of Javi who
un tío de Javi un primo de Javi el que
has done something who was a cousin of Javi
ha hecho algo que fuera un primo de Javi
or a brother of Javi to see if to see if
o un hermano de Javi a ver si a ver si
we passed the privacy by the
nos pasábamos la privacidad por los
balls or
[__] o
not How strong are they eh man how strong well that's how you
no Qué fuertes son eh tío qué fuerte pu
are and that's why
así estáis y por eso cada vez se están
more and more people are unsubscribing from your channels
desuscribo más gente de vuestros canales
my goodness yes I know it's full of that
madre mía sí sé que está lleno de eso
but but not me but not me that's not against
pero pero yo no pero yo eso no contra
Javi there No me no no me no who
Javi yo ahí No yo no no yo no quién lo
has brought it up show the evidence and such
ha sacado que muestre las pruebas y tal
And what and whoever wants to comment on it,
Y que cual y el que quiera comentarlo yo
even if they brought up evidence of everything, I'm not going
aunque sacara pruebas de todo yo no voy
to comment on that, it's not about Javi, I'm not
a comentar eso yo no es de Javi yo no
this sentence, no because it really
esta sentencia no porque de verdad que
seems to me that it can't
me parece que hasta ahí No se puede
go that far Ah no aaí no aai no aa it can't go that far
llegar Ah no aaí no aaí no aa ahí no se
eh
puede llegar eh
How are you going to comment on something about the
Cómo Vais a comentar una cosa de la
poor privacy of these people, each one
pobre privacidad de esta gente cada uno
with his conscience, each one
con su conciencia cada uno con cada uno
with his conscience eh I mean not
con su consciencia eh o sea no la
Tania's conscience eh But the
conciencia de Tania eh Sino la
conscience of the one who commented on this, of
consciencia del que ha comentado esto
course, Tania's conscience no no  no no they
claro la conciencia de Tania no no no no
are what they are family with what I do or don't
son lo que son familia con lo que haga o
do or too strong
no haga o demasiado fuerte
no And in this case if it comes out I don't understand
no Y en este caso si sale No entiendo
youtuber who deletes many words and
youtuber que elimine muchas palabras y
then stops of of putting these types of
luego deje de de de poner este tipo de
stories that I already said are too
historias que ya digo que son demasiado
delicate soledad Pérez 4 months with
delicadas soledad Pérez 4 meses con
us
nosotros
many that what that YouTube that has to
muchísimas que qué que YouTube queé
censor a public sentence
tiene que censurar una sentencia pública
that you don't understand that YouTube But if
que no entiendes que YouTube Pero si
you have done with the sentence what
ustedes habéis hecho con la sentencia lo
you wanted but here
que os había dado la gana pero aquí no
the case of Carlota Prado has not been commented on the case
se ha comentado el caso de Carlota Prado
of Marta Castillo has not been commented on
no se ha comentado el caso de Marta
the case of
Castillo no se ha comentado el caso de
Marta Riesco has not been commented on How is it that the one
Marta riesco Cómo que el el de la que a
you like not the one with which you
ti te gusta no el de con la que ustedes
get along the one from your little group
os lleváis el de la de vuestro grupito
that sentence cannot be commented on that one
esa sentencia no se puede comentar esa
has to be censored youtuber but
la tiene que censurar youtuber pero
Franco died many years ago
Franco murió hace muchos años
eh Thank you come out for
eh Gracias salidad por
renewing Ita days says I liked
renovar Ita días dice me gustó el
yesterday's live
directo de ayer
Ita But if I saw you telling me something ahita
Ita Pero si te vi diciéndome cosa ahita
ahita that I put my heart into you Wait I
ahita que te puse corazón Espérate te
put my heart into you don't worry
puse corazón mío no te preocupes
you  wait ayy my back is going away you have to
tú espérate ayy mi espalda me vo ten que
take
tomar
one let's
un a
see It seems very serious to me It seems very
ver Me parece muy grave Me parece muy
serious but but no I'm not
grave pero pero no no me posiciono en
against it
contra
ayita you have to take a pill
ayita tiene que tomar una pastilla
wait what a
espérate qué te pas
moment you have a
un momentito
serious moment out of respect I'm not going to take
grave por respeto yo no me voy a
advantage of something as serious and as
aprovechar de algo tan grave y tan
delicate as that I'm sorry but
delicado como es eso Lo siento pero
not to ask for money for cancer there respect
no para pedir dinero para el cáncer ahí
we don't give a damn
el respeto nos lo pasamos por el pomelo
no Peppa to ask for money with a
no Peppa para pedir dinero con un
relative having a relative there the
familiar teniendo un familiar ahí el
respect was not so delicate no Peppa
respeto no era tan delicado no Peppa
eh with a relative of that boy who
eh con un familiar del chaval ese que se
died of cancer eh And we ask for the money and
murió de cáncer eh Y pedimos el dinero y
then we forget about it for 7 months there is
luego se nos olvida durante 7 meses hay
respect no I'm not going to tell you more
el respeto no no te voy a decir más
Peppa Where was the respect when you
Peppa Dónde estaba el respeto cuando
had a spokesperson for a foundation
teníais a un portavoz de una fundación
against cancer and you had
contra el cáncer y teníais en llamada a
Loli Huerta on a call telling her what was
a Loli Huerta contándole lo que le
happening to her that nothing was wrong with her but she
pasaba a ella que no le pasaba nada pero
made it up there the respect what there the
se lo inventó ahí el respeto qué ahí el
respect what was Loli's privacy
respeto qué era la privacidad de Loli
was very strong or how How was that Peppa
era muy fuerte o cómo Cómo era eso Peppa
the little word that you made a mistake Peppa
la palabrita que os equivocaste Peppa
that you made a mistake and  you said that
que os equivocaste y dijisteis que que
Peppa that Loli had cancer and in the
Peppa que Loli tenía un cáncer y al
end it was a biopsy that you made a mistake
final era una biopsia que os equivocaste
the little word do you remember that you made a
la palabrita te acuerdas que os
mistake there respect you didn't care
equivocaste ahí el respeto te daba igual
no This yes This yes because this of course this Of
no Esto sí Esto sí porque esto claro
course this F you no you that I don't even
esto Claro que esto F tú no tú que yo ni
talk to Tania or anything yesterday ent here we
me hablo con Tania ni nada ayer ent aquí
gave it but your enemy is Jai
le dimos pero vuestro enemigo es Jai
Oliveira you don't care if you hate each other you don't care
oliveira te da igual si os odiáis entre
that you get together among
ustedes os da igual que os juntáis entre
all of you hate each other because the
todos los los odiáis porque el el
important one is Javi Oliveira and the center
importante es Javi oliveira y el centro
is Javi Oliveira and that's the one we
es Javi oliveira y ese es por el que
all go for
vamos todos
No look so we had to talk about this because of what
No mira tan había que hablar de esto por
had been talked about previously about
lo que se había hablado anteriormente de
de arde but I I'm not going there now Oh
de arde pero yo yo no voy ahí ahora Oh
no Because also It's that it's that this is a
no Porque además Es que es que eso es un
subject that I'm not going to
un tema que que ni de coña lo voy a
touch on it Ah whether it's true Or whether it's a lie I'm not
tocar Ah sea verdad O sea mentida no lo
going to
voy a
touch it Well, take the morning to the
tocar Pues nada llévate la mañana al
Channel and collaborate with her although well
Canal y colabora con ella aunque bueno
some will surely take the
algunos lo harán seguramente llévate la
morning and collaborate with her luxuriously
mañana y colabora con ella de lujo de
luxuriously yeah
lujo vo
yes I'm not going to touch it  but are you sure it's that
sí no lo voy a tocar pero está segura es
no I'm not going to touch it exactly sea
que no no lo voy a tocar exactamente mar
José dry and around there No, I don't know
José seco y por ahí No pues no sé
coward but they really just
cobadonga pero de verdad que me acaban
sent me a photo Right now and
de mandar ahora una foto Ahora mismo y
I feel it in my soul that you do it
yo lo siento en el alma que lo hacéis
so that I react not here Ah
para que yo reaccione yo por aquí no Ah
around there No, no Jai I'm not going to commit
por ahí No no es Jai yo no voy a cometer
the crime of what because because no what
el delito de de qué porque porque no qué
crime Because also what crime are you going to
delito Porque además que no qué delito
comment if there is a sentence Yes
vas a comentar si hay una sentencia Sí
but sasusaku is a very sensitive subject and
pero sasusaku es un tema muy escabroso y
I certainly that is too private
yo desde luego eso es demasiado privado
intimate and delicate that no it is not
íntimo y delicado que no que no es
intimate it is intimate I already know that you are finding out You're welcome
íntimo es íntimo Ya lo sé que os estáis
anora but it's something I do
enterando De nada anora pero es algo Yo
n't know if Tania is going to say it on her channel
no sé si Tania lo va a decir en su canal
Or not information that has come out from
O no una información que ha salido del
very very close environment very very
entorno muy muy allegado muy muy
close to Tania And of what happened and so if it will be I think I do
allegado de Tania Y de lo que pasó y así
n't know Tania you are
que si será yo creo no sé Tania estás
here I am invoking you Tania Tania you
por aquí te estoy invocando Tania Tania
are
estás por
here coward if I saw you on Twitter
aquí cobadonga si le visto en Twitter
Well as I don't happen around there it doesn't
Bueno pues como yo por ahí no no pasó no
happen Pepa those things that I refuse Peppa
pasa [__] esas cosas que me niego Peppa
is more of calling  your sister's ex-boyfriends
es más de llamar a los exnovios de tu
okay, I mean Peppa Peppa needs to
hermana vale o sea Peppa Peppa le falta
take Leo's teacher, she's missing that, yes
llevar a la profe de Leo le falta eso sí
eh your sister's ex-boyfriends and all
eh los ex novios de tu hermana y tod
that stuff Yeah, right Peppa That's right, no
esas cosas Sí verdad Peppa Eso sí eso
problem, that doesn't have any line or
sin problema eso no tiene ninguna línea
How little shame you really have I
ni Qué poca vergüenza tenéis de verdad O
mean with this topic I think that it's that
sea con este tema Yo creo que es que
sincerely it speaks more about you than about
sinceramente habla más de ustedes que de
anything, I mean it's why you
que que de nada o sea es que para qué
know what I'm telling you I mean with this topic
sabes lo que te digo o sea con este tema
I think that the masks no, why not
yo creo que las caretas no ya para qué
If they didn't know that there was enough, I mean,
no Si no sabían que haba lo suficiente o
a thing, man, a thing that
sea una cosa tío una cosa que la propia
Tania herself has told him that it's nothing about her
Tania la ha contado que no es nada de su
private life that she told her that she has
vida privada que le ha contado ella que
made it public and that it's a
la ha hecho pública y que es una cosa
huge thing that has a sentence and that
gordísima que tiene una sentencia y que
Tania defended that she was doing
la Tania defendió que estaba haciendo
a campaign to defend him even with what there was
una campaña para defenderlo aún con lo
eh even with what there was and she
que había eh aún con lo que había y ella
defends him and it's a person who is not
lo defiende y es una persona que no es
a relative that is I mean it's not a
un familiar que se O sea no es un
relative that is your brother your father eh
familiar que sea tu hermano tu padre eh
or someone that you have no choice but to be
o alguien que no te queda otra que sea
your relative it's a person that she had just
tu familiar es una persona que acababa
met it's tremendous  Guys, guys, I'm
conocer es tremendo chicos chicos yo me
going to go. No, I mean, it's 12. No, what do you
voy a ir no o sea son las 12 no qué
want us to see? Peppa's answer. Are you
queréis que veamos la respuesta de la
from Troy? It's gotten late? He doesn't
Peppa ar de Troya se nos ha hecho tarde
say, not even you. As innocent as always,
no dice ni tú tan inocente como siempre
believing the other day that in this they
creyendo el otro día que en esto no
couldn't put hatred first. I
podían poner por delante el odio a ti te
told you, I didn't believe it. I thought,
lo dije yo no me lo creía Yo pensaba que
no, in this tremendous thing. Guys, I don't know
no que en esto tremendo eh chicos no sé
what to do. I don't know if I should go to the salser.
qué hacer eh No sé si irme a la salser
It's that the salser, what's there?
Es que la salser qué es lo que hay